Papers of Clifford Clinton Faires, 1924-1947.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Clifford Clinton Faires papers, 1924-1947.
AZ 006
Faires, Clifford Clinton, 1877-
Correspondence, minutes of meetings, and other materials related to Faires activities with the Arizona Game Protective Association and the Arizona Wildlife Federation.
1.25 linear feet.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL:http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
none.
Biographical Note
Judge of the Superior Court, Gila County, Ariz.; Secretary-treasurer, Arizona Game Protective Association.
Organization
This collection is organized into 3 series.
Series 1: Correspondence, 1930-1947.
Series 2: Arizona Game Protective Association records, 1924-1942.
Series 3: Miscellaneous, 1940-1947.
Scope and Content Note
Correspondence, minutes of meetings, and other materials related to Faires activities with the Arizona Game Protective Association and the Arizona Wildlife Federation. Also includes correspondence on naturalization and immigration issues, 1939-1945, and I Am An American Day activities in Globe, Ariz., 1940-1947.
Access Terms
Arizona Game Protective Association -- Records and correspondence.
Arizona Wildlife Federation.
Patriotism -- Arizona -- Globe.
Wildlife conservation -- Arizona -- History -- Sources.
Game protection -- Arizona -- History -- Sources.
Naturalization -- United States -- History -- Sources.
Judges -- Arizona -- Archives.
Globe (Ariz.) -- History -- Sources.
Container List
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1930-1947.
  - Correspondence, 1930-1933. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1934. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1935. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1936. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1937. (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Correspondence, 1938. (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
  - Correspondence, 1939. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1940. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1941. (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - Correspondence, 1942. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1945. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1947. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Naturalization Correspondence, 1939-1945. (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Series 2: Arizona Game Protective Association records, 1924-1942.
  - Gila County Unit, Minutes Of Meetings. 1924-1942. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Constitution, By-laws, etc. no date. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Arizona Wildlife Federation, Bulletin. 1941-1946. (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Series 3: Miscellaneous, 1940-1947.
  - I Am An American Day. 1940-1943. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - I Am An American Day. 1944. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - I Am An American Day. 1945-1947. (Box 3, Folder 6)